We're starting an hour early, so let's get going!
I'm already on screen.
Where's that cute girl?
Where is she?
Where is that?
Oh, there she is!
So...
Today's live broadcast was like, “I've got it all wrapped up...
Like, “Is everyone all right?
Like, “Oh, it's started.
I only have a vague idea of what's going to happen.
I know you're all grinning in front of your computers, but I just found out that there's a chat box around here, and that's why we're going to start this live broadcast.
I'm sure there's some kind of chat box here, so I'd like to start the recording.
I'm recording this now, but it's going to be on-air over the New Year.
So, you know...
It's not even Christmas yet, and we're already over.
It's a time-space distortion.
We're actually experiencing it.
Before you humans.
We're from the future.
That's cool.
But I can't tell you.
The space-time police would arrest me if I told you.
You're saying it now.
I just said it.
I said it in the plot.
I'll be erased.
So I'm going to go ahead and finish.
So today is the last day of the summer.
I'm going to do a puzzle of the Devil in the museum.
It's a puzzle.
It's a puzzle as it is.
The white one is a design... or rather, you can design it yourself.
We are looking for people who can design their own puzzles, and we are asking for your help.
I'm not sure if it's just a clunker show or a clunker show, but it's a clunker show.
The Nakajima Raiya Award, like a real sabon award at the Ponkotsu Show.
Nakajima Ria Award?
I thought you read “Ponkotsu”.
It's written “Ria Nakajima” and reads “Ponkotsu”.
You read “Ponkotsu”?
A little bit about the awards.
Today, we'll include the award ceremony.
First of all...
I received so many awards.
It was hard to decide.
And, you know, that's the thing, I was probably the last one to choose.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
I'm probably picking after you two.
I don't know, maybe I chose this one better.
I'm like, “I'm glad you did it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I chose what I wanted to give you as a show.
I chose what I wanted to give as a show, and after much deliberation...
I had a lot of trouble deciding what I wanted to give the show, and I chose this one.
By the way, when the awards were announced...
The winners of the awards will be announced at the same time as the awards presentation.
For example, if it was the Nakajima Raiya Award...
For example, if it was the Nakajima Raiya Award, the winner would be given a pen name, right?
A pen name, I mean...
And then, you know, we draw a portrait of the person based on his/her image.
That's what we do best, isn't it?
That's right. We've done this a lot.
If we could do this, no one would be able to top us on terrestrial TV.
That's for sure.
They wouldn't do something like this on terrestrial TV.
That means we're number one.
Don't fuck with us!
We're the only one, and we're number one!
So, what awards are we going to give out?
I'm going to announce the Ebitu award.
Or the Nakajima Shingui Award.
Well, I don't care if it's the Star Award, or the Over-E, or the Star Award, or the Over-A Award, or the Over-A Award.
What would you like to start with? Shall we start with General Ebichu?
Yes!
Shrimp Commander...
Yes, sir.
Are you sure? Just say your name?
Yes, that's right.
The winner for prawn commander is Shimamaru-san.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Shiba, apparently.
Well, they know, don't they?
Shimamaru-san's work... this is it... you remember it, don't you?
There's a story, isn't there?
You chose this one?
There's a little bit of the famous “baccy” motif...
It's really wonderful!
It's a little surreal...
So...
Maya Maya...
Oh, you're Shimamaru?
Did you draw his portrait?
Yes, I did.
Oh, seriously?
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, then.
I'll take care of it.
Are you sure?
Shimamaru-san is here.
Female.
A woman.
I've actually met her before.
In person.
She came to the benefit several times.
I don't know...
Job change
image change
I've become like Dracula.
It's like Dracula, but now you're a wise man... well, I don't know... not a job change, but an image change? Yes.
I suddenly became like Dracula.
I became a wise man.
I don't know if he wore glasses before he became a wise man, and I apologize if he didn't, but I had an image of him wearing glasses, and although he doesn't wear them now, I remember him looking like this when I first met him.
I'm the one who guessed the wild river.
I'm sorry about before, but I'm sure you'll be happy to hear that.
If you don't mind, I'd appreciate it if you don't burn it.
It might be good fuel for the fire.
I thought Shimaaru was a boy, but I didn't know that.
I thought he was a boy... but I didn't know... he's so passionate about Ebiichu.
Thank you so much!
I'll go on then...
So, the winner of the Nakajima Uchino Award is...
The winner of the Nakajima Uchino Award is “Dancing Nippori Ebi Buddy”!
Well, I took the trouble to print this out on some precious paper, and this is Mr. Shimamaru's work.
This is Mr. Shimamaru's work. Well, this looks familiar, doesn't it?
It's so unique, isn't it?
Lovely!
She was a woman, wasn't she?
And of course, there's Nippori's work.
Isn't this amazing?
It's too good!
The texture of the bike is amazing!
She's really good at it!
It's too good!
Nippori can dance and draw too?
How come I can do it?
Are you a perfect human being?
It shows in your art.
Really...
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
So I said.
Nippori.
I painted a picture
I was allowed to paint it.
I knew it myself
I painted this picture for him.
I've painted Nippori before.
This way.
Which one? Well, this one is me, Masked Liar, and this one is Everybody dancing at nightfall.
Oh, wow! The other way around?
Well, there's a reason for this.
Yes, the green one.
I was too happy to draw it.
That's why I drew a scene of me and my dancing Japanese buddy playing rock-paper-scissors.
I see.
I don't know if it's a “goo” or a “choke” or a “par”...
Overall
It looks like a “goo” and a “choki”.
But you see, this one has a “per” in it.
There's a “per” in this too.
I love the quality of Nippori station.
It's all made of plastic.
But for some reason, it's an automatic ticket gate.
It's just as I expected.
I had to include the Nippori element.
I'd like to present this to you.
Congratulations!
Shall we go to the overage show?
Well then, let's go to the overage show.
The overage show is...
Mr. Goro from Miyagi, who sends us many pictures week after week.
Mr. Goro from Miyagi prefecture.
Mr. Goro.
I'd like to give it to Mr. Goro.
I'm sure you recognize that picture, but it's like this.
Goro's picture
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's kind of cute.
It has a unique touch.
Thank you very much.
I've never met Goro, by the way.
Oh, well...
It's a perfect image.
Oh.
I think he's a man, but since he's from Miyagi Prefecture...
I think he's like this.
He's probably like this...
Mr. Noro... he was a warlord...
I'm just wearing what's supposed to be like this.
It's true.
It's not armor at all.
That's right...
But it looks more like Date.
It's not chain mail or anything.
Because Date Masamune is a hero to the people of Miyagi Prefecture.
Of course.
So... this is for Goro.
Maybe his face looks a little like Goro's.
It's just an image.
He does look a bit like a warlord.
Like a warlord.
Like he's about to fight.
I'd like to give it to you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think there was a lot of judging going on...
How was it? I don't know, but wasn't the level of all the entries quite high?
It was very high. I feel like it was a very close call, but...
I'd like to do something like this again.
We'd like to do something like this again.
We would love to do it again.
We would love to do this again.
Thank you very much for all the entries.
There is one more prize.
Another prize?
This drawing of us and what is it?
The newest staff T-shirt debuting at the museum.
The newest staff T-shirt?
Which staff T-shirt?
Staff T-shirt? Staff T-shirt? Staff T-shirt?
What's this?
I didn't even know there was such a thing as a staff T-shirt.
It's true.
It's the first I've heard of it.
I didn't know such a thing existed.
That's amazing!
It's so cool!
We don't even have one.
It looks like a rock T-shirt.
It's the type of thing you'd find at a vintage clothing store.
I love the charcoal gray.
It's got some cracks in it, too. It looks like that.
It's so stylish!
It's amazing.
Just like that.
Sorry, I'm suddenly in Kansai.
That's amazing.
It's really nice.
That's great.
It's great.
This is for the three of you who just got it.
I'd love to give it to all three of you.
We've never seen this before.
We've never seen this design before.
I think she's saying that.
It's so cute!
That's what I mean.
Well, well, well, well.
I'll keep working on it.
I'm sure we'll have another opportunity to do something like this.
If there's anything you want to know.
If you have anything to add, please send it to the usual address.
Please send them to this address.
I'd appreciate it.
Please do.
Yes, sir.
Delivery time
This is HT.
So, first of all...
You wrote this year's Kanji characters, didn't you?
Yes, yes, yes...
You want me to bring it?
Yes, yes, yes.
My prediction was the nucleus of the revolution.
But you know the Kanji that actually turned out, don't you?
Yes, I did.
This year's Kanji.
Last year's.
Is it okay that I'm distributing it?
This year's Kanji was “Kim”.
That's why it didn't come out.
That was close.
It was so close!
Where was it?
But it's like...
I feel like we're going to meet someday?
I don't know, maybe they'll meet somewhere.
Revolution and money?
I mean, money, like a revolution for the sake of money, that kind of thing.
You are very kind in your own way, Master, and you are being very kind to me right now.
Thank you very much.
If you're so far off, you should at least say so.
You're right, it's not that exciting.
It's not very exciting.
It would have been a million dollars if we had won.
Yes.
I made a mistake with that feeling.
So, that millionaire thing...
Yes.
Unfortunately, no.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
That was a lot.
One million none.
I'm sorry...
That's what I meant.
On the contrary...
From your side.
Hmm?
I don't know...
Uh...
I have to give you a present.
I missed it.
It's a little risky.
Why not?
Some kind of New Year's gift for the viewers.
I see.
Wait a minute.
Can I have a minute?
What is it?
My bag is so heavy!
What's in my backpack?
I don't see a lot of stuff in there... but it's open without hesitation, and I'm on it.
What's in it?
It's on this side, so it's in there, right?
Mosaic it.
I can't stream it.
Really?
Human Mosaic.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, yes, yes.
There's a lot of stuff in here.
Are you sure?
Yes.
What's this?
What is this?
It's okay to put it out.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What is this?
A mat.
That's a mouse pad that's no longer in use.
Mouse pad.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I don't know what to do.
It's so big, it's not real. It's not real. It explodes in your stomach?
It's warm! I'm trying to hide the fact that I'm cold.
I'm cold, but I don't really use it anymore.
Well, on the contrary, I've been having some trouble with it.
You don't mind? I'd like a big pad.
I'd like to have a big magic pad... or this one... for when it's cold... that I've used.
I'd be happy to sign it for you.
It's like they're taking a bunch of them.
There's a lot of weird stuff in here.
What the hell?
This is etiquette!
I don't want this.
I don't need this?
When you sweat...
I don't need a body sheet!
I can buy it, I can buy it, I don't need it, I don't need it, it's on the range, and I'll change it
I don't need that inflection car body sticker, it's not much, it's not a computer that moves around a lot, I want it, I want it, I want it, etch - this is really not!
iPad!
Is this good?
It's not good, it's not good, it's not good.
I'm using it.
It's like you're taking really good care of it.
I love it.
Can I keep the case?
But I don't need it that much.
I don't need it.
It's heavy and gentle.
You know, you're not all that nice.
I just got punched in the face, and now you're being nice to me.
I'm starting to have mixed feelings.
I don't want it too much. I don't want it to be heavy.
But you can use it for something.
If you use it that way, there's an infinite number of ways to use it.
As for the iPad...
Really? It's as good as a computer.
It's almost as good as a computer, so, yeah.
Well, I'm sure it's a bit of a pain in the ass for the recipient, so...
I can only see the search history... and the images...
I'm going home.
I'm going home... so I'd like to know what's in the bottom of the push button...
I just bought it, but I don't want to know the bottom of the push button... Is this hetro?
I want this!
I just bought it!
Sennheiser!
It's gonna break!
The zipper's gonna break.
Sennheisers are tough.
You know what?
It's got some kind of liquid in it.
Liquid?
What's this? It's got some kind of liquid in it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's perfume.
Perfume.
That's perfume.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's no good.
You use it.
Yes, I do.
There's a lot of liquid in there too.
What?
Two perfumes.
And a big one.
So this is how it's done, right? And a big one, too.
Like this.
Not many people put it on their face.
And it's a dose.
Smells good.
There you go.
You smell like an adult.
I don't mind if you do.
It's all over your face.
If that's the case, it's still fine.
It's not on your face, it's on your clothes. It's okay, but if that's the case, it's still okay. - It's not something you put on your face, it's something you put on your clothes. It smells really good.
- It's also good on the skin. Oh, that's right. It's for clothes.
- You're putting too much on. I'm running out.
- How about this? That's fine.
- I'll keep this one. No, not that one.
- I'll give you all this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, there's an egg on it.
Oh, wow!
Look, there's a real one!
I'm definitely a Unimaruchchi now.
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
Now that we're all unimals, I'd like to share with you...
Please, please, please, please, please!
I really can't.
Can I put three of these together?
Why do I have to give you three?
Three? Just because you misspelled a kanji...
Three? Why just one mistake?
It's been a year. A year's worth of work.
If it's not too heavy...
Well, well, well... can I close this?
Is there anything else in here?
Anyway, it's really heavy.
There's an iPad in there....
The iPad wasn't that heavy.
No, it's like when you put it all together.
It smelled great because of all the masters.
It smells amazing!
I'm sorry. I'm sure.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know.
Shouldn't you shake it more lightly?
You should shake it lightly.
Are you sure?
Then say Tamagotchi.
You can eat the tamagotchi.
I'm fine.
I'll take a logo, too.
That's funny.
I'm using it properly, just a little bit here and there.
Don't say that about the logo.
The logo's already damaged.
I feel a little sorry for you.
The staff said we had to have it.
What kind of harassment is this?
I feel sorry for Tamagotchi, too.
They've been doing it for a year, and they're attached to it.
This kind of production isn't popular on TV now.
You know, it's like being sent out to a village on your own.
This kind of bullying is so 20th century.
It's a 20th century production.
You know, they say it's a dream.
They want you to enjoy it.
What you're saying and what you're doing are different.
What I say and what I do are two different things. That's the best part for me.
I don't like people like that.
I don't want to be that person. The series begins.
Rumor has it you said something nuanced about not having to be so sad.
I didn't say that.
I'm just saying that it's going to be passed on to the viewers, but please say it in a few syllables.
I'm a foster parent, right?
If you really get it, will you buy it for me? I'm sure they'll do their best... No.
Can I take it home now?
The last one.
If I give you the food now, please give it to me.
What?
I might be full.
If you're full, can I just go?
Why are you so obsessed with this Tamagotchi?
I'm asking you to stick to it.
Only Tamagotchi.
The comments section says you're full of shit.
It's true.
I don't like this kind of thing.
What are you going to do about it?
I'll think about it.
Come on.
Let's have a meeting later.
Okay, I'm going to take it back then.
You said so much.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
It's okay.
I think it's better this way.
It's fine.
It's just the atmosphere.
It's like, “Go for it!
That's a relief.
I felt like I was taking my own child.
I can't tear him away from you.
Okay, well...
Eggs, please, everyone, forget about this for once.
This one...
And two other things.
Both signatures.
Wouldn't it be nice if they chimed in?
That's how I feel!
Let's consider including it.
Oh, consider?
Include it?
We'll have to decide on one meeting of some sort.
One for the Devil Festivo in the museum.
Oh, for one?
Yes, sir.
One?
One.
What?
Which one is it?
This one's better.
It's soaked in Rhea's scent.
This one glows.
It glows when you plug it in.
What's glowing?
Around here, it's real.
That's amazing.
Can I try plugging it in?
USB.
A lot of people want a mouse pad.
It's really expensive.
I'm going to say this.
It's a USB-A type.
Maybe that's it... just stick it in your computer. If it has a power supply.
But C or Type C?
That's right, that's right, that's right.
USB-A.
It's a big one.
Wait a minute... type C... that's right...
Wait a minute...
I'm here if you have a converter
I wonder if there is one...
I wonder if it's there.
I wonder if there's a light in the outlet.
It doesn't glow.
Plug it into the computer.
The color is serious.
It's a mouse pad.
No one plugs the mouse pad's USB cable
No one plugs a mousepad into a wall outlet.
Of course not.
That's why this product is called Laser.
If you connect it to the app, it lights up the way you like.
Why didn't you say that first?
what is this?
I thought I was getting a conversion.
You mean if you connect it to a computer or something like that?
Yes, yes, yes, it does light up.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
Then it's just for the fun of it.
Yes, it is.
I don't know if it'll be this one.
No, no, no, no, no. Thank you.
It's such an important item.
I'm so grateful.
How long have you had this?
How long have you had this for?
I bought a new mouse pad.
I bought a new mouse pad, so I don't use her anymore.
So I was like, “I don't need it, you don't need it.
Well, it's for a different purpose.
So you have a lot of things to do with it.
That's right.
The mouse pad industry has its own problems.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well... That's why.
By the way...
I'm sorry to inform you that
It's on hold.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Please do not use the mouse pad
Please don't use it as a foot towel in the bathroom.
The water supply is not that good, folks.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But if it's that long...
Yeah, that's the way it should be.
It's just right.
That's for sure.
Yes, yes, yes.
And the other thing...
Yes, yes.
The Devil Festival in Lenoir.
Yes.
Official merchandise?
We're extending the order period for these random trading cards.
If you're a member of the Nagatoreka family, you can order these.
We had already closed the order period, but we'd like to extend the order period and deliver them to you.
We'd like to extend the order period and deliver them to you all.
Wristband
The one that glows.
It glows somewhere.
Click.
It's like that.
I'm so happy.
These two are
Extension
Extended
I did
Extension, sir.
Extended!
By all means, by all means, from the tbk mall.
There's a mall in Hinata called the Hinata Mall.
It's a great mall where you can buy anything you want.
it changes everything in the world... even love...
Thank you, thank you.
I'll change everything in the world. I'll change love!
We have a lot of events and announcements today.
But one last thing... who's had a happy birthday lately? Among them...
Yes! Me?
Am I right? Yes!
What? What are you doing?
Wait, you're not giving me your stuff, too, are you?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
What's this?
Get in the box, get in the box...
Thank you!
ah, ah, now it's a berth berth! Converse!
I wonder what kind...
There's so many kinds of Converse these days.
Oh! Cool!
Wow!
I see.
Thick-soled shoes?
Thick-soled Converse!
Cute!
I'm so happy! Thank you!
If I wore them before, they would be over 2 meters long, wouldn't they? I'm sure it's going to be over 2 meters.
That's too much!
Thank you! And the one with a zipper.
How fashionable! I'm so happy! Thank you so much! I will wear it a lot!
You have good taste! Thank you!
I think it would hurt to get kicked with these.
No, it would hurt.
I've played soccer before.
It's pretty strong and heavy.
He's cute.
Toe kick, toe kick.
Toe kick.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Thank you.
Well, well, well, well.
That's how it is, sir.
So this is how it's going to be, then?
Oh, Mimi...
Happy Birthday and a Happy New Year!
I received a devil charge!
Thank you very much for the devil charge, I've turned 28 years old
Usually, but I don't really know what to say...
I started the age difference by saying I've been 23 here in this studio for the past five years, but that's not true at all.
I've been saying that's not true at all and I've been repeating it for how long this trial will last.
How long is this trial going to last?
I'd like to believe he's not mistaken, since that's what he says.
We're asking him how old he really is because we want to believe him.
I'm a newcomer who has 28 households, but I've received a devil's charge from Mr. Hyakushiki.
You're 56 years old...
No, no, no...
No... no... no... no...
What do you mean?
You mean you're smiling at me?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's up, but...
But not 56.
That's for sure.
I'd be in trouble if I was 56 like this.
They're a little too tight.
Maybe too tight, maybe too much. I mean, it would really add up.
We get a lot of visitors in the summer.
Happy birthday to Maya Maya Maya Maya Maya Mania was great, thank you very much 28
I hope you have a great new year, and I'm just going by what I said last time, not what you think I said.
I'm 28.
I'm 28 this year.
You turned 28 this year.
I am.
I'll be 28 next year.
I'll be 28 forever
Time and space are a little bit distorted.
In the history of each and every time.
It's about time.
I'm not going to disclose my age.
It's a little late for that.
That's funny.
Suddenly I'm 29 years old.
Suddenly I don't have to disclose my age.
Thank you very much.
So you're not doing the live broadcast next week?
Yes, I will.
You're taking a break for a while, right?
That's right.
After the new year?
Yes.
Well, then, it's been a real year for all of us.
Thank you so much for watching our live broadcasts and, of course.
Thank you so much for watching our live broadcasts and for paying your bills.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
So, Happy New Year!
Have a Happy New Year!